What is kindness? Is it the speed with which I run to you?
What is it that makes you say, "Bye, bye"?
what do you think of the end of your efforts to see the horizon beyond which there is no horizon?
Do you remember the flowers of suburbia?
Hello, everyone!
Hello everyone, I'm Iroha Okuda, a student of Yorigata 46.
Today is the fourth street live!
Today, my best friend and we are in the same unit.
I'm Iyoki Mao.
I was asked to participate.
Mao-chan, I brought you.
I'm so glad.
I'm so happy to be able to participate in this event, because I've always wanted to be a part of the Logio Live,
So it's just the two of you. Two?
Seino!
We have a unit called "Comeore!
We have a unit called "Comeore" and we will be doing a show in the future.
You just jumped out at me, didn't you? That's right.
We will be performing at a place called Atelier Plaza Isesaki.
What's this?
It's a sacred place for Yudesan's street live performances.
That's amazing! And I'm so excited to hear that we'll be playing in the exact same place.
But you know, I'm looking forward to it. It's kind of dependable. It's nice to know that I'm not alone, and we've practiced together a lot,
I'm going to do my best so that everyone can enjoy it this time.
The weather is getting better now, isn't it?
It's going to be fine from now on.
Yo!
Shall we do it?
Oh, no, I'm nervous.
All right, let's gut it.
How do you do it?
How do we get it in?
Ingamutibo.
Okay, here we go.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, I didn't want a wedding.
I'm sorry, I didn't want to do the wedding.
I don't know how much I really thought about it.
We could talk about anything... and we had a similar sense of humor.
I could step in with the friends I meet
Oh, the hearts of people and the scenery Too close for the eye to see
There were salvia flowers
There was a salvia flower
At the end of that summer I finally noticed
The bright red flower living in my hand throw
The feelings that I wished to see
Yes, I'd overlooked it, now that I'd seen it
It's a precious flower
I remember now
There was a salvia flower
That untied the sky
I couldn't even answer you.
Do you remember the salvia flowers?
The quiet breeze that greeted me in the flower bed at the entrance
I wanted to be blown by the wind
I wish I could hold your hand and wave to you
I wish I could hold your hand and wave
I want to hold your hand and wave it
I wish I could grab those hands and wave them
A little flower in the wind
That's how love begins.
That's right, I'm eating my favorite pumpkin pudding
I'm eating it alone.
I'm celebrating here. A wedding.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous.
Nervous.
So this is how it's going to be.
Wow, you always play by yourself like this.
Yes, I do.
That's great.
You can come closer if you want.
I'm using it.
Shortgrade.
Yes, it is.
How old are you?
18?
I'm 18.
Same age?
About the same age.
Yes, we are the same age.
I'm in my nineteen's.
Is she that cute?
I'm very happy to meet her.
I'm glad.
Next time, next time,
I've got the spirit.
The spirit.
This is...
I'm very excited.
Now, look at the next song.
The paper bag you were holding in your arms ripped open
LaFrance rolled down.
Goodbye fell off the edge of your mind
To an unpredictable tap.
I watched the whole thing, this side of the road.
I was too calm, that's what went wrong.
If only I could run more emotionally
Gently, it was time for the bus
I could have been.
I don't know what kindness is
Is it the speed with which I run to you
Or picking up the tears that fall together
I thought about the meaning of love and its value
But I couldn't find the answer
All I could do was just to do my best
I just let you go without saying a word
That's what makes us happy
If time passes by with small regrets
Don't let it come back to you
Let's stop reminiscing
And choose solitude
What is kindness?
Is it the speed with which I run to you
Or is it to pick up the tears that fall together
I've thought about the meaning of love and its value
But I couldn't find the answer
All I could do was just well
What is kindness?
Is it the speed with which I run to you
Or is it picking up the tears that fall together
I thought about the meaning of love and its value
But I couldn't find the answer
All I could do was just well
Still I'm dreaming a dream
Life's Strongest
It's not clear
asyway
Thank you very much
I'm so far away today.
I wonder if you could come closer?
Hello.
You know us?
You've never heard of us before?
Thank you very much.
My name is Mao-chan and this is her first time at LogioLive.
Mao-chan! Good luck!
I'll do my best.
Iroha, my name is Iroha.
Iroha's already done about three logio live shows at YouTube's house!
I've been doing live shows for a while.
That's great.
What a surprise. This place is famous.
This is the place, isn't it?
I want you to do well.
Yes, I'd be honored.
Okay, next song.
Yes, sir.
Let's hear it.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Please listen.
Music
music
I'm glad you like it!
The next song is a little bit sad and sad.
Please listen to it!
I'll be right back.
Well, don't go to sleep.
You're impatient, aren't you?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Maple syrup.
I think I'm happy.
The antique wall clock is ticking.
It went by so fast, I didn't even notice.
I wonder if it's broken.
I chuckled at that.
No one calls me master
No one calls me "Master" these days
I'm watching over you from behind the counter
I shook my head
I don't know why I'm so sad to say good-bye
just because I won't see you for a few hours
I slowly let go of our joined hands
I can't lose the warmth of your hand
like a magnet
I can't help but cling to you like a magnet
Love is about holding on to what's left of you
I turn my head again and again to make up my mind
your little hand in mine
the way your back makes me want to call your name
I want to call your name
I love you so much
I wonder why it is so sad to say good-bye
So that I can see you again tomorrow
Why is it so sad to say good-bye
Why does it make me sad?
Just because I won't see you for how many hours
I slowly let go of our joined hands
I don't want that warmth to fade away.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I've played a lot of things,
I don't want to finish yet.
Thank you very much.
Finally.
Yes, ma'am.
Please turn it off.
Seino
Rusty compass
The rusty compass needle
Where does it point?
Brain, come on, the magnet of madness
Is still alive
How many adventurers
I've lit the paths of the wayward
Now I'm on my first journey
The wilderness of my youth
Everyone says it's a hardship
But I'm not ashamed to be frightened
I'm not ashamed of anything
I can't make up my mind
You may fall down, but that's the way it's supposed to be
Instead of standing still, keep moving forward
Even if you fail in the middle of your ambition
It's better to dream for once
Beyond the horizon I've never been to
What do you think of the end of your efforts
When the sun burns out
And the darkness of this world
I think I'll come to a point
There will never be a life without regrets
There is no such thing as a life without regrets
No one will see it that way
They leave something behind that they wish they'd done
Neckties.
If you fall down alive, it's for real.
Look, we're standing still.
Move on now, even if you fall short of your ambition
I'd rather dream for once
I'd rather avoid a horizon I've never seen
What do you think you're doing because you've tried so hard?
When the sun burns out
And the darkness of this world will come
Break a leg
Thank you very much.
Please watch it on YouTube.
I'm watching my favorite snacks.
Thank you.
We're done.
It's over.
It was my first logio live.
I was so thrilled.
You're happy with your eye shot.
I was so excited.
I've been a huge fan of yours for a long time.
So I was really happy to be able to do it.
And at the end of the show, there were a lot of people there.
It was a lot of fun.
I was happy that people who knew us and people who didn't
I was happy to see people who knew us and those who didn't.
I'm glad to be able to
I can tell.
I hope to see you all again someday, take a walk!
Please subscribe and rate our channel!
Thank you for watching.